1. [Legal Information](https://parsecgaming.com/en/legal)
2. Privacy Policy Hub

Privacy Policy Hub

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------

This Privacy Policy governs our information practices for our Developer Services, which includes any websites, where a link to this Policy is provided. Developer Services means products and services intended for a party that develops and/or distributes a game or other app made with and/or using Unity Services.

This Privacy Policy also applies to Personal Information we collect offline, such as when you call us or interact with Unity in person, such as at an industry event or at a place of business.

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

These FAQs provide a handy entry point to our longer and more comprehensive [Developer Privacy Policy](https://parsecgaming.com/legal/developer-privacy-policy). They are intended to enhance rather than replace the important notices in the Privacy Policy, which governs our collection, use, storage, and sharing of the information that we collect or receive from you. **Customers should understand that Unity does not provide legal advice, therefore the information on this page is not a substitute for seeking your own legal counsel to determine the legal requirements of your business and processes, and how to address them.**

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

This Privacy Policy will provide you with information on how Unity Technologies will collect, use, store, share or otherwise handle your Personal Information that we are responsible for and collect or receive through your use of applications which are owned by third parties but utilize Unity’s technology.

This Privacy Policy also applies to Personal Information we collect offline, such as when you call us or interact with Unity in person, such as at an industry event or at a place of business.

[Technical and Organisational Measures including Technical and Organisational Measure to ensure the Security of the Data](https://unity.com/legal/technical-and-organisational-measures)
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Technical and Organisational Measures (TOMs) are strategic safeguards designed to protect data security and ensure adherence to data protection regulations. These are incorporated by reference in Unity’s [Data Protection Addendum.](https://unity.com/legal/unity-data-processing-addendum-dpa)

-------------------------------------------------------

Sub-processors are third-party companies that assist Unity by handling personal data on Unity's behalf. These are incorporated by reference in Unity’s [Data Protection Addendum](https://unity.com/legal/unity-data-processing-addendum-dpa).

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

These FAQs provide a handy entry point to our longer and more comprehensive [Game Player and App User Privacy Policy](https://unity.com/legal/game-player-and-app-user-privacy-policy).They are intended to enhance rather than replace the important notices in the Privacy Policy, which governs our collection, use, storage, and sharing of the information that we collect or receive from you.

---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

This sets forth Unity’s policies and procedures regarding the Unity software products in schools.

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

This sets forth special privacy terms regarding use of the Unity MARS Companion App.

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

In 2021, the European Commission and the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commission issued new Standard Contractual Clauses ("2021 SCCs"). Additionally, in 2022, the UK Parliament approved the UK International Data Transfer Addendum to the EU SCCs (“UK Addendum”). The 2021 SCCs and UK Addendum replace the Standard Contractual Clauses enacted in 2010 (“2010 SCCs”). This is a pre-signed copy of this document which you may download, execute on your side, and return to DPA@unity3d.com.  

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

This notice explains Unity's processing activities with respect to Personal Information collected through users of Generative AI Tools  

Language

Social

Currency

CurrencyBRLCNYJPYKRWUSDEUR

USD

Purchase

Education

Download

Unity Labs

Resources

Unity

Copyright © 2024 Unity Technologies

"Unity", Unity logos, and other Unity trademarks are trademarks or registered trademarks of Unity Technologies or its affiliates in the U.S. and elsewhere ([more info here](https://unity.com/legal/trademarks)). Other names or brands are trademarks of their respective owners.
